Guide to the Barrett Gallagher photographs and film, 1932-1989
Gallagher, Barrett photographs and film, 1932-1989
- Series IV. Contact Prints
  - Contact Prints (Oct 1960 - May 1961), Cornell: (Box 44)
    - Balch dormitory cafeteria, a University service, 98-10-29
    - Dean J.W. McConnell, Industrial and Labor Relations, Arbitrator, 98-30-36
    - Office of Financial Aids, 100-01-13
    - Professor F.A. Long, Chemistry, 100-14-28
    - Math Library, White Hall, 100-29-35
    - Quad, Olin library, 101-01-16
    - Construction, Industrial and Labor Relations, 101-17-23
    - Library, Olin library and Ezra Day Hall, 101-24-36
  - Contact Prints (1961 -1967), Cornell Home Economics (Box 45)
  - Contact Prints (Jan 1962 - Mar 1964) (Box 46)
  - Contact Prints (Apr 1964 - Jun 1965) (Box 47)
  - Contact Prints (Jan 1966 - 1968) (Box 48)
  - Contact Prints (May 1969 - Mar 1973) (Box 49)
  - Contact Prints (Oct 1970 - May 1974) (Box 50)
  - Contact Prints (Jun 1974 - Dec 1977) (Box 51)
  - Contact Prints (Jan 1978 - Dec 1986) (Box 52)
  - Contact Prints (Feb 1987 - Nov 1990) (Box 53)
- Series V. Slides
  - Slides (Feb 1939), Fortune 1 (Box 54)
  - Slides (Jul 1953 - Jan 1960), Fortune 2 (Box 55)
  - Slides (Jul 1960 - Nov 1969), Fortune 3 (Box 56)
  - Slides (1939 - 1972), Covers B &W (Box 57)
  - Slides (1952 - 1965), Carriers (Box 58)
  - Slides (Jun 1953), Korea USS Lake Champlain (Box 59)
  - Slides (1955 -1956), USS Forrestal (Box 60)
  - Slides, New York Shipyard Fortune May 1962 Sixth Fleet 1956 (Box 61)
  - Slides, Time Saturn V 1966 (Box 62)
  - Slides, Saturn V Apollo Fortune 1967 Time 1966 (Box 63)
  - Slides, Verrazano Narrows Bridge Mar 1963 - Dec 1965 Fortune 1965 (Box 64)
  - Slides, Newsweek 1969 McCalls Dayton Graphic Color 1970 Stamford Holland 1969 (Box 65)
  - Slides (Dec 1970 - Dec 1985), Radio City Christmas Tree (Box 66)
  - Slides (Aug 1976 - Aug 1982), Liberty Park (Box 67)
  - Slides (Jan 1950 - Aug 1955) (Box 68)
  - Slides (May 1956 - Sep 1961) (Box 69)
  - Slides (Jan 1963 - Jun 1970) (Box 70)
  - Slides (Jul 1970 - Jan 1977) (Box 71)
  - Slides (Jan 1977 - Oct 1979) (Box 72)
  - Slides (Feb 1980 - Feb 1984) (Box 73)
  - Slides (Feb 1984 - Apr 1987) (Box 74)
  - Slides (Apr 1987 -) (Box 75)
- Series VI. Prints
  - Prints (1932 - 1980), Cornell Drama Club (Box 76)
  - Prints (Prints 1934 - 1966), Performing Arts (Theater, Music, Dance) (Box 77)
  - Prints (1934 - 1977), Wedding Prints Ingrid Bergman P. Draper D. Farrand Livingston N. Rockefeller (Box 78)
  - Prints (1934 - 1990), Framed and Unframed Prints Magazine Covers (Box 79)
  - Prints (1935 - 1988), Timmie and Barrett Gallagher (Box 80)
  - Prints (1935 - 1956), Fortune Armed Guard Bluenose Flattop South Fleet (Box 81)
  - Prints (1942 - 1945), WW II Armed Guard (Box 82-83)
  - Prints (Feb 1939 - Mar 1952), Fortune Drummond Tom Ewell Mitch Miller Dark Legend (Box 84)
  - Prints (1942 - 1944), Armed Guard SS Cape Henlopen Egypt 1942 Cape Town Biera Majellan Guantanimo 1943 (Box 85)
  - Prints (1942 - 1944), Armed Guard SS Powers (Box 86)
  - Prints (1942 - 1945), WW II Armed Guard WW II Wall (Box 87)
  - Prints (1942 - 1961), USS Forrestal USS Independence Florida Bonefish (Box 88)
  - Prints, World War II Mounted (Box 89)
  - Prints, World War II Print Books (Box 90)
  - Prints (1943 - 1944), Navy DE 528 (Box 91)
  - Prints (1943 - 1944), Navy DE 528 (Box 92)
  - Prints (Jan 1944 - Sep 1945), World War II (Box 93)
  - Prints (1944 - 1956), Flattop World War II Korea (Box 94)
  - Prints (1944 - 1956), Flattop World War II Korea (Box 95)
  - Prints (1945 - 1947), World War II (Box 96)
  - Prints (1944 - 1945), World War II (Box 97)
  - Prints (Nov 1944 - May 1958), Military (Box 98)
  - Prints (Oct 1946 - Jul 1980) (Box 99)
  - Prints (May 1948 - Feb 1978), Liberty Park Waterfront Duplicates (Box 100)
  - Prints (Jun 13 - Jul 29, 1953), SS Lake Champlain (Box 101)
  - Prints (Jun 1953 - Jun 1958), Flattop Lake Champlain Enterprise Forrestal Sixth Fleet (Box 102)
  - Prints (1948 - 1959), Bonefish Korea (Box 103)
  - Prints (Jun 1953 - Jan 1962) (Box 104)
  - Prints (1955 - 1966) (Box 105)
  - Prints (Aug 1955 - Oct 1968) (Box 106)
  - Prints (May 1955 - May 1961), Forrestal (Box 107)
  - Prints (Sep 1956 - Oct 1956), Suez Canal (Box 108)
  - Prints (Sep - Oct 1956), Sixth Fleet (Box 109)
  - Prints (Jul 3 - Sep 15, 1957), Strikeback (Box 110)
  - Prints (Jun 12, 1957 - Jul 18, 1963), Bainbridge Attack Tower Raleigh (Box 111)
  - Prints (May 1958 - Apr 1967), NAEC Guam Ranger Reliance Independence Sea Gulls Quehanna Gypsum Quein Domecon (Box 112)
  - Prints (Nov 1959 - Mar 1963), New York City Helicopter (Box 113)
  - Prints (Nov 1959 - May 1963), New York City (Box 114)
  - Prints (Nov 1959 - May 1963), New York City Duplicates (Box 115)
  - Prints (May 1959), USS Independence CVA 1962 May 1969 USS United States (Box 116)
  - Prints (Sep 1959 - Jun 1980), View From Studio 7 Studio 7 (Box 117)
  - Prints (Mar 1960 - May 1960), Cornell (Box 118)
  - Prints (Mar 1960 - Mar 1965), Cornell (Box 119)
  - Prints (Oct 1960 - May 1962), Constellation CVA 64 (Box 120)
  - Prints (Apr 1960 - Apr 1967), Cornell (Box 121)
  - Prints (1960 - 1969) (Box 122)
  - Prints (1960 - 1969), Verrazano Bridge (Box 123)
  - Prints (1960 - 1969), Clouds Verrazano Bridge New York City (Box 124)
  - Prints (Oct 1960 - Aug 1970), Seagulls Waterfront Snow Storm (Box 125)
  - Prints (Jul 1961 - May 1962), Task Group Alfa New York Naval Shipyard (Box 126)
  - Prints (1961 - 1967), NASA Jastrow (Box 127)
  - Prints (Aug 1961 - Sep 1969), Institute For Space Studies Seminars (Box 128)
  - Prints (Apr 1961), Iceland (Box 129)
  - Prints (Aug 1961 - Aug 1971), Repetitive Strobe Balloons Pool Paul Draper Jastrow (Box 130)
  - Prints (May 1962 - 1970) (Box 131)
  - Prints (Mar 1963 - May 1964), Bridge I (Box 132)
  - Prints (Mar 1963 - Dec 1965), Bridge II (Box 133)
  - Prints (Sep 1963 - Mar 1967), NASA Saturn V Time Fortune (Box 134)
  - Prints (Sep 1963 - Sep 1967), Saturn V Apollo (Box 135)
  - Prints (Jun 4-8, 1962), Sam Houston (Box 136)
  - Prints (Sep 1963 - Aug 1967), NASA (Box 137)
  - Prints (Sep 1963 - Aug 1967), NASA (Box 138)
  - Prints (Sep 1963 - Aug 1967) (Box 139)
  - Prints (Apr 1964 - Aug 1967), NASA NASAland (Box 140)
  - Prints (1963 - 1966), Saturn V Apollo Pad A Pad B (Box 141)
  - Prints, Verrazano Bridge Arecibo 1974 Route 17 (Box 142)
  - Prints (Jul 1964 - Aug 1967), Robert Jastrow Field Trips CBS - TV (Box 143)
  - Prints (Dec 1965 - Jan 1966), Lincoln Center Lennie and Isaac Stern (Box 144)
  - Prints (Sep 1968 - Jan 1970), USS John F. Kennedy CVA 67 (Box 145)
  - Prints (Feb 1969 - Dec 1977), Christmas Lights (Box 146)
  - Prints (1970), Birds Bronx Zoo New England Botanical Gardens (Box 147)
  - Prints (Jan 1970 - May 1977), Downtown Manhattan (Box 148)
  - Prints (1970 - 1979), Jastrow Liberty Park Arecibo Christmas Tree Fireworks Route 17 Harer Surprise Party Sandra Martus (Box 149)
  - Prints (1970 - 1979) (Box 150)
  - Prints (1970 - 1979), Fireworks Tulips 9 West 57th - NYC Christmas Lights (Box 151)
  - Prints (Feb 1971), East Africa (Box 152)
  - Prints (Feb 1971), East Africa (Box 153)
  - Prints (Feb 1971 - Dec 1972), Africa (Box 154)
  - Prints (1971 - 1972), East Africa Africa Duplicates (Box 155)
  - Prints (Feb 1971), Africa (Box 156)
  - Prints (1971 - 1972), Africa (Box 157)
  - Prints (Mar - Apr 1972), East Africa Safari II (Box 158)
  - Prints (1971 - 1972), Africa (Box 159)
  - Prints (Mar-Apr 1972), East Africa Safari (Box 160)
  - Prints (Dec 1976 - Oct 1982), New York City (Box 161)
  - Prints (1971 - Dec 1976), Christmas Lights (Box 162)
  - Prints (1976 - 1977), Liberty Park (Box 163)
  - Prints (Nov 1977 - Apr 1989), Cornell: Johnson Museum Exhibit Performing Arts Center President Rhodes (Box 164)
  - Prints (Feb 1976 - Dec 1980), New York City (Box 165)
  - Prints (1980 - 1981), Snow Fences Johnson Museum (Box 166)
  - Prints, Flowers New York City Christmas Lights Fireworks Gainsborough (Box 167)
  - Prints, New York City Tulips Fences Radio City Christmas Tree Christmas Lights (Box 168)
  - Prints (Dec 1983 - Dec 1988) (Box 169)
  - Prints (1980 - 1990), Fences Flowers Christmas Tree Fireworks (Box 170)
- Series VII. Color Transparencies, Tear Sheets and Magazine Covers
  - Color Transparencies (Box 171)
  - Tear Sheets (Box 172)
  - Magazines, Life - The Engineer Fortune Nov 1963, May 1967 Infinity July 1968, Nov 1970, May 1971 Leica Photography (Box 173)
  - Popular Photography, Sept 1981 May 1984 Time Dec 1978 Modern Photography Jan 1988 New York Oct 1981 Life - The Engineer Johnson Museum Exhibit Booklet Cornell Alumni News: Nov 1967; Dec 1974; May 1984; Jun 1990; Jun 1971; Apr 1981; Feb 1989; Apr 1983 (Box 174)
- Series VIII. Texts, Papers
  - Texts, including "Witness to War: The Photographs of Edward Steichen and His Associates," exhibition catalog (1994) (Box 175)
  - Texts, Ledger, Letters, Misc. Papers (Box 176)
  - Expense Account Books, Address/Date Books (Box 177)
- Series IX. Oversize Prints
  - Oversize Prints (1960 - 1970), Jastrow Ticker tape Parade USS Bainbridge New York City Dr Papanicalov Dr Romanov Dr Conway Dr Moore Route 17 9 West 57th (Box 178)
  - Oversize Prints (1948 - 1956), USS Forrestal USS Philadine Korea Xerography Santa Fe "21" Babson Map Champion Paper Gypsum Queen Radio City Christmas Tree New York City 1963 - 1965 Arecibo 1974 (Box 179)
  - Oversize Prints (Jun 1947 - Jan 1955), Xerography Babson Map Mitch Miller and Family Burgess Meredith Paulette Goddard Florida Paul Draper Korea Budapest Quartet (Box 180)
  - Oversize Prints (Jul 1963 - Dec 1972), Mac Kriendler Route 17 Studio 7 (Box 181)
  - Oversize Prints (Feb 1949 - Aug 1950), Mickie Miller Xerography Babson Map Bellevue USS United States April 1969 Africa 1972 Arecibo 1974 Radio City Christmas Tree 1977 (Box 182)
  - Oversize Prints (Jun 1954 - Dec 1979), Paul Draper Guggenheim Museum Radio City Christmas Tree "21" New York City US Naval Academy USS United States N. Mailer Jastrow Kit Peak C. Sagan (Box 183)
  - Oversize Prints (May 1956 - Oct 1960), New York City USS Independence Individuals Sept. 1963 - Sept 1970 Lenny Bernstein J. Rudel New York Philharmonic Snowy Owl NASA Onyx Club - 1938 (Box 184)
  - Oversize Prints (Sep 1956 - Dec 1965), Sixth Fleet Hans Bethe Verrazano Bridge 6 Day Bike Race Harpo Marx (Box 185)
  - Oversize Prints (Jan 1938 - Apr 1940), Benny Goodman Burgess Meredith Paul Robeson Cozy Cole Ingrid Bergman Julius Caesar Orson Wells Cornell (Box 186)
  - Oversize Prints (Apr 1946 - Sep 1948), Bonefish Florida Raytheon Sea Bee Burgess Meredith Paulette Goddard (Box 187)
  - Oversize Prints (Aug 1976 - Sep 1981), Liberty Park (Box 188)
  - Oversize Prints (Oct 1937 - May 1945), Blue Nose China Sea Armed Guard World War II China Sea World War II Marc Mitsher (Box 189)
  - Oversize Prints (1949-1979), Battleships Submarines Mitch Miller Tony Bennett Paul Draper Burgess Meredith Larry Bell (Box 190)
  - Empty (contents now in Box 189) (Box 191-192)
  - Magazine Covers and Prints, US Naval Institute Dec. 1965 Colliers Aug. 1942 Fortune July 1945 Cornell Alumni News April 1981 Cornell Alumni News 1979 Camera 35 1958 NY HQ USA Infinity Nov. 1970 Flattop Cornell Reports March 1981 Cornell Alumni News Sept. 1960 Cornell Alumni News Nov. 1967 Fortune May 1947 Fortune Nov. 1948 Fortune Aug. 1959 Fortune May 1967 Prints: Arecibo New York City NASA Jastrow Verrazano Bridge Bell Aircraft Sixth Fleet Forrestal Article On 35mm Lenses Lake Champlain The Champ Perry Como Mitch Miller RCA Television Raytheon Bluenose President Farrand Daisy Farrand Eleanor Roosevelt with Flora Rose Dean Kimball Dean Ogden Cornell Drama Club Alexander Drummond Franchot Tone Ingrid Bergman Photos for articles for Fortune Magazine: US Watch Works UN Building Information Center On Lake Champlain Xerography Air Craft Super Charger SS Wilfred Sykes - Ore Carrier Manhattan - Sunnyside Yards Mesabi Duluth Photos For Articles For Fortune: Supreme Court 1947 Merck Chemical Co. Lever Brothers Steuben Glass, Inc. Ford Electronized Chemicals The Republican Party - Taft (Box 193)
  - Empty (contents now in Box 193) (Box 194)
  - Matted Photos and Posters, New York City East Africa (Box 195)